{
  "status": "success",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Go to the Dogs' means-------",
      "answer": "be ruined",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["be ruined", "run fast", "go for dog", "go after dog"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The idiom'rides the high horse' means------",
      "answer": "feel proud",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "feel proud",
        "keep away from ",
        "put blame on other",
        "at the end"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The idiom ' to drive home ' means--------",
      "answer": "to emphasize",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "to emphasize",
        "to find one's roots",
        "to return to place of rest",
        "back to original position"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Identify the meaning of the idiom from the given sentence. ( HE 'KICKED THE BUCKET')",
      "answer": "died",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["died", "forgot", "destroyed", "cheated"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The idiomatic expression ‘head over heels’ means ——.",
      "answer": "excited",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["excited", "intelligent", "nonsense", "proud"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the idiom ‘to cut corners’ means?",
      "answer": "To do something badly or cheaply to save money or time",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "To do something badly or cheaply to save money or time",
        "To hide something from someone or somewhere",
        "To say or argue throughly",
        "D) To save something very expensive"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Complete the following sentence using the appropriate idiom. (balu passed the exam ------)",
      "answer": "with flying colours",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "with flying colours",
        "by and large",
        "by fits and starts",
        "is black and blue"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the meaning of the given idiom ‘To pick holes’ .",
      "answer": "to criticize someone",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "to criticize someone",
        "to find some reason to quarrel",
        "to destroy someone",
        "to eat some part of an item"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Write the correct meaning of the idiom ‘pros and cons’ .",
      "answer": "Favourable and unfavourable factors",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "Favourable and unfavourable factors",
        "on the whole",
        "The difficult situation",
        "good condition"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'Hear on the  grape wine'.",
      "answer": "spread rumours",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "spread rumours",
        "over here",
        "here from distance",
        "here from a nearby place"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'go to the dogs'",
      "answer": "be ruined",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["be ruined", "feel proud", "to die", "excited"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'rides the high horse'",
      "answer": "feel proud",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["feel proud", "be ruined", "excited", "to die"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'Kick the bucket",
      "answer": "to die",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["to die", "feel proud", "excited", "be ruined"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'head over heels'",
      "answer": "excited",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["excited", "to die", "be ruined", "feel proud"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'to cut corners'",
      "answer": " to do something badly or cheaply to save money or time",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        " to do something badly or cheaply to save money or time",
        "successfully",
        "to criticize someone",
        "favourable and unfavourable factors"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'with flying colours'",
      "answer": "successfully",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "successfully",
        " to do something badly or cheaply to save money or time",
        "feel proud",
        "here from distance"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'To drive home'",
      "answer": "emphasize",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["emphasize", "successfully", "feel proud", "excited"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'Pros and cons'",
      "answer": "favourable and unfavourable factors",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "favourable and unfavourable factors",
        "favourable and unfavourable factors",
        "favourable and unfavourable factors",
        "feel proud"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Meaning of the idiom 'Here on thegrape wine",
      "answer": "spread rumours",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "spread rumours",
        "successfully",
        "emphasize",
        "favourable and unfavourable factors"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What does the underlined idiom mean: so many employee‘got the axe’ as the company was underline financial excise.",
      "answer": "lost the job",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "lost the job",
        "have no idea",
        " out of one's mind",
        "angry and overcome"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The meaning of the idiom is parish pump is ——.",
      "answer": "local politics",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["local politics", "charity", "sacred offerings", "state of alarm"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Pick out the nearest in meaning: To fly off the handle.",
      "answer": "To lose one’ s temper",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "To lose one’ s temper",
        "To dislocate",
        "to take off",
        "to be airborne"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Bring out the meaning of the idiom to the following sentence (we shall fight tooth and nail for our right.",
      "answer": "with all our power",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "with all our power",
        "using teeth",
        "peacefully",
        "without soldiers"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "A wild goose chase means:",
      "answer": "something pointless",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "something pointless",
        "a useful attempt",
        "chasing a goose",
        "killing a goose"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "The idiom swan song means ——.",
      "answer": "the last public performance of an artist or athlete",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "the last public performance of an artist or athlete",
        "musical performance",
        "song of a swan",
        "NOT"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "To read between the lines means ——.",
      "answer": "to understand the hidden meaning of the writer",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "to understand the hidden meaning of the writer",
        "to suspect",
        "to read carefully",
        "to do useless reading"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct options for the following: crocodile tears",
      "answer": "fake tears",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "fake tears",
        "a competitive sales environment",
        "false sense of bravery",
        "absence without permission"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "His most trusted friend proved to be a snake in the grass.\r\nWhat does a snake in the grass means ——.",
      "answer": "a hidden enemy",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "a hidden enemy",
        "an unreliable person",
        "low and the mean",
        "cowardly"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means greasing the palm.",
      "answer": "bribery",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["bribery", "breakdown", "break away", "break the ice"]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Got the axe",
      "answer": "lose the job",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "lose the job",
        "local politics",
        "To lose one’ s temper",
        "with all power"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Parish pumps",
      "answer": "local politics",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "local politics",
        "lose the job",
        "with all power",
        "To lose one’ s temper"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  To fly off the handle",
      "answer": "To lose one’ s temper",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "To lose one’ s temper",
        "local politics",
        "lose the job",
        "with all power"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Tooth and nail",
      "answer": "with all power",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "with all power",
        "lose the job",
        "local politics",
        "To lose one’ s temper"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Wild goose chase",
      "answer": "something pointless",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "something pointless",
        " last performance",
        "to understand the hidden  meaning of the writer",
        "fake tear"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Swan song",
      "answer": " last performance",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        " last performance",
        "to understand the hidden  meaning of the writer",
        "fake tear",
        "something pointless"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  To read between the lines",
      "answer": "to understand the hidden  meaning of the writer",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "to understand the hidden  meaning of the writer",
        " last performance",
        "something pointless",
        "fake tear"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Crocodile tears",
      "answer": "fake tear",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "fake tear",
        "to understand the hidden  meaning of the writer",
        "something pointless",
        " last performance"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Snake in the grass",
      "answer": "hidden enemy",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "hidden enemy",
        "bribery",
        "a pleasant or easy situation",
        "at the last moment"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Greasing the palm",
      "answer": "bribery",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "bribery",
        "at the last moment",
        "to understand the hidden  meaning of the writer",
        " last performance"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  A bed of roses",
      "answer": "a pleasant or easy situation",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "a pleasant or easy situation",
        "at the last moment",
        "the beginning and the end",
        "be born in very rich family"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means   At the eleventh hour",
      "answer": "at the last moment",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "at the last moment",
        "a pleasant or easy situation",
        "be born in very rich family",
        "the beginning and the end"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Alpha and Omega",
      "answer": "the beginning and the end",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "the beginning and the end",
        "at the last moment",
        "a pleasant or easy situation",
        "be born in very rich family"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  Born with a silver spoon in ones mouth",
      "answer": "be born in very rich family",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "be born in very rich family",
        "a pleasant or easy situation",
        "at the last moment",
        "the beginning and the end"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means   At hand",
      "answer": "near",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["near", "from original source", "in jail", "same type person"]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  At first hand",
      "answer": "from original source",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["from original source", "near", "same type person", "in jail"]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means   Behind the bars",
      "answer": "in jail",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["in jail", "from original source", "near", "same type person"]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means   Birds of a feather",
      "answer": "same type person",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": ["same type person", "in jail", "from original source", "near"]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means   Nip the bud",
      "answer": "stop in the beginning",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "stop in the beginning",
        "to get an unexpected fortune",
        "same type person",
        "near"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "which of the following idiom means  To get a windfall",
      "answer": "to get an unexpected fortune",
      "moreDetails": "",
      "arr": [
        "to get an unexpected fortune",
        "stop in the beginning",
        "near",
        "from original source"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
